♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
I can’t remember the equation.
The square root of
a quotient equals uh…
Uh, zero?
Uh, no. Ten?
No, wait. I give up.
Hey, wait! Where are you going?
To study for the science final.
It's tomorrow and I can't exactly
count on you to help me.
You must be kidding!
We'll miss the afternoon snack!
And don't get all worked up
about that exam!
I've got a little something in mind.
This little something.
Does it start with cheat, and
end in cheat, by any chance?
Wow! You just read my mind!
Oh, forget about your dumb plan.
Gee thanks a lot, Ulrich,
for being so supportive.
Wow, I am really knocked out!
Bet you can't guess why!
Don’t tell me!
The members of the band
Love Potion split up?
Come on. That’s old news, you dork!
Brian fell in love with Crystal Pearl,
and so Geoffrey kicked them out!
Now listen to this, huh.
The news is…
my father said it was
okay to use the gymnasium!
He said yes?
Mmhm.
Yes!
I've gotta find William!
Oh, it’s going to be the dance
party of the century!
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
Hurry it up!
You two! Take those mats
into the storage room.
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
You! Push that pommel horse
against the wall!
Come on! Move it!
Oh, no!
I don’t believe this!
So it’s really true, huh?
The principle gave the
techno party the green light?
It looks like it. Yeah.
Wow! Smoking, huh?
The best DJ’s from all the
local schools will be there.
It’s gonna be a blast!
I’m not blasting anything.
The mixing board is hammered!
I can’t figure out how to fix it.
Hey, no problem.
We’ll ask Jeremie.
He’s Mister Fix-It.
He can fix anything.
You think so?
Yeah!
No!
I got better things to do with my time
than play around with a mixing board.
Maybe I can help.
Would you?
Uh, but what about our
research on your antivirus?
I’m just sitting around
watching you at this stage.
Great! Come on!
What about the science final?
Don’t you ever study?
It’s in the bag!
(GROANS)
So, then…
This is the thing
that makes the music?
Yup.
You play the records on the turntables.
The board mixes one song with another.
The trick is to synchronise the sound.
Interesting.
It doesn’t sound like you know an awful lot about it.
Will it take much longer?
No. I’m done.
Mind if I give it a try?
Huh. Hey, it's working!
Aelita, fantastic!
You want to try?
Well, yeah.
Why not?
Wow!
I’ve never managed
to get that kind of mix.
Hey, goof-offs!
Well, don't mind me!
Do you know what
time it is by any chance!
Uh, we’re really sorry, Jim.
We’re rehearsing for tomorrow night.
Do you like techno?
Forget about it.
(SCOFFS) Electronic music.
I prefer the twist!
Aelita, you really mix like a pro.
Where’d you learn?
Uh…um…
Uh, it runs in the family!
We’re all artists. We’re creative!
I’ll make a selection of LP’s,
and you can be our DJ!
Tomorrow night!
Okay?
You think so?
Well, uh, okay!
You’re wasting your time with this party.
I am not wasting my time.
I’m trying to live. Like you guys.
And have some fun -- a good time.
That’s human too, isn’t it?
You mean you don’t have a good time
researching the antivirus with me?
You’re as stubborn as a fool!
It’s stubborn as a mule!
Odd, you didn’t study at all?
Nope.
But like I told Jeremie, it’s in the bag.
Huh? What’s going on?
Can’t we go in?
Inspection by G.I. Jim.
(MILITARY DRUMLINE)
One pen! That’s all you can take in!
Ouch.
That’s an unexpected development.
Mhmn.
You have two hours for physics,
and then two hours for chemistry.
My colleagues and I will
correct the exams this afternoon.
After that, the principal himself
will announce the results.
You may begin.
(SIGHS)
The test is over!
Put your pens down
and stay where you are
While I collect all of your papers.
Stay in your seats
until I have all of them!
Hmm.
Well done, Odd.
That’s…one of your best yet.
Misses Hertz…
Hertz, ah, Hertz…
I hope she’ll let me keep
Odd’s paper swan for my collection.
Huh?
(UNNERVING MUSIC)
Well?
Sure, never felt better.
I was talking about your exam, stupid.
It looks like I’m gonna
be left back this year.
Oh, don’t exaggerate.
But it wouldn’t have
killed you to study a little.
Cut it out.
This is not the time.
Hey, we’re gonna see Aelita the DJ!
That’s bound to cheer us up!
Where is she, by the way?
She’s already in the gym.
The DJ’s get VIP treatment.
What about Jeremie?
He’s sulking.
You are not going, and that is that!
But please, daddy!
It’s the happening of the century!
You should have thought of that earlier
and studied for the exam!
(UNNERVING MUSIC CONTINUES)
XANA!
He sure picks his moments.
Desert sector. Okay.
Oh, no!
(TECHNO MUSIC, CHEERING)
Aelita?
A question for the school paper!
As a DJ, how would you define your style?
Hardcore, deep house, or downright new beat?
Um…
She’s a little too nervous to answer.
I’d say her style is more hardcore,
but it’s more a style of her own.
Totally rad!
Tada!
You snuck out?
No, no.
My father said,
“you’re gonna repeat the year,
"but it’s no big deal, sweetie.
Doesn’t mean you can’t
have a good time!”
Is that what he said?
Oh, you’re such an idiot!
Of course I snuck out.
What do you think?
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
And now Aelita!
A brand new DJ!
And as you’re gonna see,
She totally rips!
Wow, it’s great.
You coming?
Your cousin's incredible, Odd!
Mhmn!
Kiwi!
Come here, boy!
Come on! Good boy!
Kiwi!
Help!
Come here you mangy mongrel!
Oh--oh, nice doggy!
Go on. Chew through the rope.
Kiwi, no!
Come back!
That mutt is as brainless as his owner.
Oh…
Huh?
Kiwi, this is no time for games.
You have to go and get
Odd and the others
from the gymnasium, you hear?
Now go get Odd!
Yeah! That's a good dog!
Run!
Ugh. With my luck, he’ll
come back with the principal.
What’s up?
Not dancing?
Nah, it’s not my thing.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me. Come on!
Let me see how you move!
Oh. You’re right.
It’s not your thing.
(BARKS)
Nice dog sounds.
Where did Aelita sample that from?
Hey, what are you doing here, buddy?
Jim will spot you!
Okay, okay, okay.
Hold on. I’m coming.
Hey!
Where you going?
Ask him.
I’ll go with you.
I could use some fresh air.
Uh…I forgot I have
something important to do.
Uh, what?
I have to, uh, polish
my flip-flops! Heh heh…
Bye!
(SCREAMS)
(MUSIC STOPS, CLAMORING)
What happened?
It was Jim!
XANA’s possessed him!
Where’s Aelita?
At the dance.
She’s finishing her mix.
With Jim around?
Everything’s alright.
She just fainted.
I’ll take her into the infirmary.
Go on with your party.
(MUSIC CONTINUES,
INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT)
Are you sure that
Jim can virtualize Aelita
and send her to Lyoko?
Under XANA’s control,
he can do anything.
Oh, no.
Aelita doesn’t stand a chance
alone against the scyphozoa.
And she can say bye-bye to her memory.
They’re not here.
Hurry. Let’s head for the factory.
At your order, XANA.
Transfer Aelita.
Virtualization.
(UNNERVING MUSIC)
Jeremie, Yumi, take the corridor.
Odd and I will take care of Jim.
Okay!
If you ask me, it’s more likely
he’s gonnna take care of us.
(GROANS)
And he’s brought a friend
along with him, too.
Go!
Bonsai!
This is bad.
You think so?
Hiyah--aah!
Ulrich!
Aelita!
Are you okay?
Let’s say I’ve been better.
Hang on.
Help is on the way.
(GROWLS, SNARLS)
Ulrich?
This is no time to take a nap.
We’ve got an invincible guy to wipe out.
What are you suggesting?
The puppet thing!
Like the way we
handled the Kankrelats.
Hey, Jim!
You didn’t think a little tap like that
would knock me out, did you?
Hiyah!
Hurry up!
Yeah!
We’re on the way.
Get to the scanner room now!
Hang on, Aelita!
The scyphozoa isn’t here yet.
But please hurry.
Transfer Ulrich.
Transfer Yumi.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Yumi.
Scanner Odd.
Scanner Ulrich.
Virtualization!
The crater isn’t far.
Head south-southeast!
Have you programmed the vehicles?
Of course. I think of everything.
So does XANA, I guess,
from the looks of it.
You got company.
Faster! If the scyphozoa
gets there before you do,
Aelita's done for!
Go on ahead.
Leave the hornets to me.
Go!
Come on.
Laser arrow!
Rats! I missed!
Odd, you’re down to 10 life points.
They’re heading for the crater.
Careful! The hornets are right behind you!
But you’re not far now.
You’re there!
Gotcha.
Agh!
Ulrich!
Move it, Yumi! Go on!
Surprise!
Taxi?
Jeremie, it’s here.
Not so fast, blubber-face!
Yumi!
Hiyah!
Yumi! Oh, no!
(SCREEHCING)
Whoa!
The scyphozoa’s
stealing her memory!
Odd, Ulrich, hurry!
Hey! What the…
Jim! Uh--
Sorry. I’m taking over from here.
No!
(THUNK)
Hold on tight!
Not bad, huh?
I--
Hey!
(CHUCKLES)
Jeremie, what level is
Aelita’s memory at?
Huh?
Hiyah!
Jeremie!
Jeremie, you there?
Hoo--ha! (YELLS)
Oh, no!
Jeremie!
Get back to the computer!
We’ll handle Jim.
Jeremie, you there?
I’m back, Ulrich.
It’s up to you. Hurry!
Huh?
Super sprint!
Get to the activated tower.
25 degrees east! Move it!
Jeremie!
Ulrich, hurry up!
Move it!
Tower deactivated.
Huh?
What am I doing here?
You’ll never know, Jim.
Return to the past now.
Okay, so that’s a promise, right?
Jeremie, you’re gonna
help me with physics.
And Aelita, you’re gonna
help me with chemistry.
And you’re gonna
help me until I get it!
Right?
Promise.
Wow, I am really knocked out!
Bet you can’t guess why!
Your father said okay
for the gymnasium?
Huh?
How did you know that?
Well, I’ve already lived through this day
and I just traveled back through time.
You’re a real looney.
I feel sorry for you.
By the way, you wanna
come and study with us?
Jeremie and Aelita are
gonna give us a hand.
Study? Me?
(SCOFFS) Looks like you lost the
only brain cell you had left!
If she only knew what was coming.
What a pitty.
After final exams, I want you
to teach me about techno.
I love it! It’s my new earthly passion.
Will you come listen to me mix, Jeremie?
I promise.
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO